# **GIOVANNI P. MONTEROLA**

Agdao, Davao City, Philippines 8000 +639309404172 / giovannimonterola@gmail.com

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Experienced Virtual Assistant for 6 years. Most of the jobs as Virtual Assistant have been in Web Development, particularly web-based applications and systems. Familiar with using PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML and CSS tools. Also, had been in Real Estate and different Internet Marketers and Employers Experienced also in EBAY, SHOPIFY and AMAZON platforms. A self-motivated individual that can work independently and also a good team player.

### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:**

2011-2015 BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STI College Davao

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

•	Knack Developer	Business Marketing Engine	August 2020 - August 2021
•	Web Developer	Perfect Body Shaper	February 2019 - August 2020
•	ICT Support	Noble Manhattan	September 2016 - August 2020

#### **SKILLS:**

- Knowledge of MS Office / MS Excel
- Knowledge of Google Docs / Google Sheet
- Computer Troubleshooting
- Knowledge of WordPress and Shopify
- Experienced on Aweber, Get Response and MailChimp

- Lead Generation
- Admin and Personal Assistant
- Knowledge on Infusionsoft
- Knowledge on Onlywire
- Knowledge on Photoshop
- Amazon and Ebay Manager
- Knowledge in ManyChat
- Email, Social and Video Marketing

## **QUALIFICATIONS:**

- Dedicated and hardworking individual
- Willing to render overtime

- Willing to learn
- God-Fearing